http://firstpeople.us/FP-Html-Forums/privacy.html

First People :: Privacy Policy.
Cookies | Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The artists that sell craft/artwork on the site all hate spam and will never pass on any details to a third party.
Log Files
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Our site does not use cookies. However, some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.
DoubleClick DART cookies
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's
DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are
browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising
(including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is
used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest
based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based
on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been
viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas
hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as
on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable
information". It does NOT track personal information about
you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone
number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit
card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites
using this advertising by visiting https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.
However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.
This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.
Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
Necklaces [2]
James King - Diné [Navajo]
Edward S. Curtis [A]
American Indians [B]
American Indians [C]
American Indians [G]
American Indians [H]
American Indians [I]
Other
Tipi, Wigwams etc. [D]
Sailing Vessels [E]
Pottery and Basketry [F]
Sensitive Photopgraphs
Animal Photographs
Scott Denny [Wolves etc.]
Tim Denny [Wolves etc.]
Michael Cummings [Wolves Only]
Bill Maynard [Wolves Only]
Monty Sloan [Wolves]
